Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards U.S. House of Representatives papers, Inclusive: 1990-2010, Bulk: 1991-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Clippings, 1991-2010; 13
  - Topical, 1992-2005; 8
    - Redistricting, 2003 May 19-21 (Box 240, Folder 14)
    - Redistricting, 2003 May 22-25 (Box 240, Folder 15)
    - Redistricting, 2003 May 26-29 (Box 240, Folder 16)
    - Redistricting, 2003 May 30-31 (Box 240, Folder 17)
    - Redistricting, 2003 June 1-3 (Box 240, Folder 18)
    - Redistricting, 2003 June 4-5 (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Redistricting, 2003 June 6-7 (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Redistricting, 2003 June 8-10 (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Redistricting, 2003 June 11-30 (Box 241, Folder 4)
    - Redistricting, 2003 July 1-15 (Box 241, Folder 5)
    - Redistricting, 2003 July 16-31 (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - Redistricting, 2003 Aug (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - Redistricting, 2003 Sept (Box 241, Folder 8)
    - Redistricting, 2003 Oct (Box 241, Folder 9)
    - Redistricting, 2003 Nov (Box 241, Folder 10)
    - Redistricting, 2003 Dec (Box 241, Folder 11)
    - Redistricting, 2004 Jan (Box 241, Folder 12)
    - Social Security, 2002 (Box 241, Folder 13)
    - Terrorism, 2001-2002 (Box 241, Folder 14)
    - Transportation, 2001-2002 (Box 241, Folder 15)
    - US Representative Henry Hyde, 1996 (Box 241, Folder 16)
    - US Representative Steve Stockman, 1995 (Box 241, Folder 17)
    - Veterans (1 of 3), 2001-2002 (Box 241, Folder 18)
    - Veterans (2 of 3), 2002 (Box 241, Folder 19)
    - Veterans (3 of 3), 2002 (Box 241, Folder 20)
    - Veterans, Capital Asset Realignment for Enhanced Services (CARES), 2005 (Box 241, Folder 21)
    - Veterans, Jim Nicholson, 2005 (Box 241, Folder 22)
    - Votes, 2002 (Box 241, Folder 23)
- Correspondence, 1991-2010; 14
  The Correspondence series is arranged into General, Approved Texts, Constituent Mail, and Members and VIPs. Approved Texts is arranged by topic and then date. These include draft letters in response to constituent mail and include the following topics: Agriculture, Budget, Defense, Education, Ethics, Foreign Affairs, Human Services, Social Security, and Veterans Affairs. Many of these drafts have handwritten notes by Edwards or his staff. Constituent Mail is grouped chronologically and contains emails, form letters, handwritten letters, and personal correspondence from the congressman’s constituents regarding a wide range of topics. Members and VIPs is arranged alphabetically by date, and contains correspondence from members of the U.S. House of Representatives and other important persons.
  - General, 2001-2002; 2009; 1
    - Department of Veterans Affairs List Request, 2002 (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Franked Mail Plan, 2001 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook Letters, 2009 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Approved Texts, 1993-2001; undated; 2
    - General, undated (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Affairs, 1993 (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - General, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - Agriculture, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - Bank, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 9)
    - Community, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 10)
    - Defense, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 11)
    - Economy, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 12)
    - Education, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 13)
    - Election, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 14)
    - Environment, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 15)
    - Ethics, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 16)
    - Health, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 17)
    - Interior, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 18)
    - Judicial, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 19)
    - Labor, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 20)
    - Science and Technology, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 21)
    - Social Security, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 22)
    - Tax, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 23)
    - Veterans Affairs, 1994 (Box 242, Folder 24)
    - General, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - Community, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Defense, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Economy, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Energy, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Environment, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Ethics, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - Health, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - Housing, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 10)
    - Human Services, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 11)
    - Judicial, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 12)
    - Labor, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 13)
    - Science and Technology, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 14)
    - Social Security, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 15)
    - Tax, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 16)
    - Trade, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 17)
    - Transportation, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 18)
    - Veterans Affairs, 1995 (Box 243, Folder 19)
    - General, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 20)
    - Agriculture, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 21)
    - Bank, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 22)
    - Budget, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 23)
    - Communications, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 24)
    - Community, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 25)
    - Congratulations, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 26)
    - Defense, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 27)
    - Economy, 1996 (Box 243, Folder 28)
    - Education, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Election, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - Energy, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - Environment, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - Ethics, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - Health, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - Housing, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - Human Services, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - Interior, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 10)
    - Judicial, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 11)
    - Labor, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 12)
    - Postal Service, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 13)
    - Science and Technology, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 14)
    - Small Business, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 15)
    - Social Security, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 16)
    - Tax, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 17)
    - Thanks, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 18)
    - Trade, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 19)
    - Transportation, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 20)
    - Veterans Affairs, 1996 (Box 244, Folder 21)
    - General, 1997 (Box 244, Folder 22)
    - Agriculture, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Communications, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - Defense, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - Economy, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - Education, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - Election, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - Energy, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Environment, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - Ethics, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 11)
    - Health, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 12)
    - Human Services, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 13)
    - Interior, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 14)
    - Judicial, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 15)
    - Labor, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 16)
    - Postal Service, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 17)
    - Science and Technology, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 18)
    - Small Business, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 19)
    - Social Security, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 20)
    - Tax, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 21)
    - Thanks, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 22)
    - Trade, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 23)
    - Transportation, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 24)
    - Veterans Affairs, 1997 (Box 245, Folder 25)
    - General, 1998 (Box 245, Folder 26)
    - Agriculture, 1998 (Box 245, Folder 27)
    - Bank, 1998 (Box 245, Folder 28)
    - Budget, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Communications, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Congratulations, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Defense, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Education, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Election, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - Energy, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - Environment, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - Ethics, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 10)
    - Grants, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 11)
    - Health, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 12)
    - Housing, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 13)
    - Human Services, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 14)
    - Interior, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 15)
    - Judicial, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 16)
    - Labor, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 17)
    - Postal Service, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 18)
    - Science and Technology, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 19)
    - Small Business, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 20)
    - Social Security, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 21)
    - Tax, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 22)
    - Trade, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 23)
    - Transportation, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 24)
    - Veterans Affairs, 1998 (Box 246, Folder 25)
    - Community, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 26)
    - Health, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 27)
    - Housing, 1999 (Box 246, Folder 28)
    - Social Security, 1999 (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - General, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Abortion, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Agriculture, 2000 Sept-Oct (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Animal Welfare, 2000 Oct-Nov (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Banking, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Census, 2000 Oct 4 (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - Children, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - Civil Rights, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 10)
    - Communications, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Justice, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 12)
    - Defense, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 13)
    - Disabilities, 2000 Oct 24 (Box 247, Folder 14)
    - Drugs, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 15)
    - Education, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 16)
    - Elections, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 17)
    - Energy, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 18)
    - Environment, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 19)
    - Flags, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 20)
    - Foreign Affairs, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 21)
    - Foreign Aid, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 22)
    - Gambling, 2000 Oct 12 (Box 247, Folder 23)
    - Government Affairs, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 24)
    - Gun Control, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 25)
    - Health, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 26)
    - Housing, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 27)
    - Hunger Relief, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 28)
    - Immigration, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 29)
    - Interior, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 30)
    - Judicial, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 31)
    - Labor, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 32)
    - Legislation, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 33)
    - Library of Congress, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 34)
    - Medicare, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 35)
    - Privacy, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 36)
    - Private Property, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 37)
    - Retirement, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 38)
    - Science and Technology, 2000 Sept 22 (Box 247, Folder 39)
    - Senior Citizens, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 40)
    - Services, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 41)
    - Social Security, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 42)
    - Tax, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 43)
    - Tobacco, 2000 Oct 10 (Box 247, Folder 44)
    - Trade, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 45)
    - Transportation, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 46)
    - Veterans, 2000 (Box 247, Folder 47)
    - General, 2001 (Box 247, Folder 48)
    - Budget, 2001 (Box 247, Folder 49)
    - Defense, 2001 (Box 247, Folder 50)
    - Delayed Mail, 2001 (Box 247, Folder 51)
    - Education, 2001 (Box 247, Folder 52)
    - Energy, 2001 (Box 247, Folder 53)
    - Environment, 2001 (Box 247, Folder 54)
    - Health, 2001 (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Labor, 2001 (Box 248, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Affairs, 2001 (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Member Letters, 1992-2010; 3
    - A-Z, 1992 (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - A-Z, 1993 (Box 248, Folder 5)
    - A-C, 1994 (Box 248, Folder 6)
    - D-M, 1994 (Box 248, Folder 7)
    - N-Z, 1994 (Box 248, Folder 8)
    - A-C, 1995 (Box 248, Folder 9)
    - D-F, 1995 (Box 248, Folder 10)
    - G-N, 1995 (Box 248, Folder 11)
    - Q-S, 1995 (Box 248, Folder 12)
    - A-C, 1996 (Box 248, Folder 13)
    - D-F, 1996 (Box 248, Folder 14)
    - G-L, 1996 (Box 248, Folder 15)
    - M-P, 1996 (Box 248, Folder 16)
    - R-Z, 1996 (Box 248, Folder 17)
    - A-C, 1997 (Box 248, Folder 18)
    - D-F, 1997 (Box 248, Folder 19)
    - G-K, 1997 (Box 248, Folder 20)
    - L-P, 1997 (Box 248, Folder 21)
    - R-T, 1997 (Box 248, Folder 22)
    - U-Z, 1997 (Box 248, Folder 23)
    - A-C, 1998 (Box 248, Folder 24)
    - D-F, 1998 (Box 249, Folder 1)
    - G-K, 1998 (Box 249, Folder 2)
    - L-P, 1998 (Box 249, Folder 3)
    - R-T, 1998 (Box 249, Folder 4)
    - U-Z, 1998 (Box 249, Folder 5)
    - A-C, 1999 (Box 249, Folder 6)
    - D-F, 1999 (Box 249, Folder 7)
    - G-K, 1999 (Box 249, Folder 8)
    - L-P, 1999 (Box 249, Folder 9)
    - R-T, 1999 (Box 249, Folder 10)
    - U-Z, 1999 (Box 249, Folder 11)
    - A-Z, 2000 (Box 249, Folder 12)
    - A-Z, 2001 (Box 249, Folder 13)
    - A-Z, 2002 (Box 249, Folder 14)
    - A-Z, 2003 (Box 249, Folder 15)
    - A-Z, 2004 (Box 249, Folder 16)
    - A-Z, 2005 (Box 249, Folder 17)
    - A-Z, 2006 (Box 249, Folder 18)
    - A-Z, 2007 (Box 249, Folder 19)
    - A-Z, 2008 (Box 249, Folder 20)
    - A-Z, 2009 (Box 249, Folder 21)
    - A-Z, 2010 (Box 249, Folder 22)
    - A-Z, undated (Box 249, Folder 23)
    - Mammoth Thank You’s, 2009 (Box 249, Folder 24)
  - 1991-1992, 4
    - General (1 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 249, Folder 25)
    - General (2 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - General (3 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - General, Requests, 1991-1992 (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - General, Thank You, 1991 (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - General, Thank You, 1992 (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Abortion, General, 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 1)
    - Abortion, Freedom of Choice Act (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 2)
    - Abortion, Freedom of Choice Act (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 3)
    - Abortion, H.R. 2611: Pregnancy Counseling Act, 1991 (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - Abortion, H.R. 3090: Assistance for Family Planning Services, 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 5)
    - Abortion, Pro-Choice, 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - Abortion, Pro-Life, 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 7)
    - Abortion, Title X (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 8)
    - Abortion, Title X (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 9)
    - Abortion, Waco Planned Parenthood Clinic, 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 10)
    - Agriculture, General, 1991-1992 (Box 251, Folder 11)
    - Agriculture, Dairy, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Farm Credit System, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture, Private Property Rights Act, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - Armed Forces, General, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Armed Forces, Ft. Hood, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - Armed Forces, Health Care, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Armed Forces, Military Benefits, 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 7)
    - Armed Forces, National Guard (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 8)
    - Armed Forces, National Guard (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - Arts, National Endowment for the Arts (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 252, Folder 10)
    - Arts, National Endowment for the Arts (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - Banking, General, 1991-1992 (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - Banking, Bosque County Bank, 1992 (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - Banking, H.R. 6: Reform the Deposit Insurance System, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - Banking, H.R. 3542: Escrow Account Reform Act, 1991 (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - Banking, Interstate Branching, 1991-1992 (Box 253, Folder 6)
    - Banking, Truth in Savings Act, 1992 (Box 253, Folder 7)
    - Banking, “Super IRA”, 1991-1992 (Box 253, Folder 8)
    - Budget, General (1 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 253, Folder 9)
    - Budget, General (2 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 253, Folder 10)
    - Budget, General (3 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - Civil Rights, 1991-1992 (Box 254, Folder 2)
    - Cities, A-Z, 1991-1992 (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - Communications, General, 1991-1992 (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - Communications, Radio, 1991-1992 (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - Communications, Telephone, 1991-1992 (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - Communications, Television (1 of 4), 1991-1992 (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - Communications, Television (2 of 4), 1991-1992 (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Communications, Television (3 of 4), 1991-1992 (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - Communications, Television (4 of 4), 1991-1992 (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - Criminal Justice, General, 1991-1992 (Box 255, Folder 5)
    - Criminal Justice, Prison Overcrowding, 1992 (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - Defense, General (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 255, Folder 7)
    - Defense, General (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Defense, Budget Cuts, 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - Defense, Peace Dividend, 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Defense, Persian Gulf (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Defense, Persian Gulf (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Defense, V-22 Osprey Program, 1992 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Education, General, 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Education, Corporal Punishment, 1991 (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Education, Excellence in Education Act, 1991 (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Education, Higher Education, 1991-1992 (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Education, Student Aid, 1991-1992 (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - Energy, General, 1991-1992 (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Energy, Electrical, 1991-1992 (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - Energy, Energy Department, 1991-1992 (Box 257, Folder 7)
    - Energy, Gas Prices, 1991-1992 (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Energy, Oil, 1991-1992 (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Environment, General (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Environment, General (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Environment, Air Quality, 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Environment, Animal and Wildlife Protection (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Environment, Animal and Wildlife Protection (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Environment, Animal Testing and Cruelty, 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - Environment, Endangered Species Act, 1991-1992 (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Environment, Pollution, 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Environment, Rain Forests, 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - Environment, Soil and Water Research, 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - Environment, Water Projects, 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Environment, Water Quality, 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Affairs, General (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Affairs, General (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Affairs, Africa, 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Affairs, Europe and Asia (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Affairs, Europe and Asia (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Affairs, Latin America, 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Affairs, Middle East, 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Affairs, Panama Canal, 1992 (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Government Affairs, General (1 of 4), 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Government Affairs, General (2 of 4), 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Government Affairs, General (3 of 4), 1991-1992 (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - Government Affairs, General (4 of 4), 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Government Affairs, Campaign Finance Reform, 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Government Affairs, Congressional Pay Raise, 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Government Affairs, Congressional Spending, 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Government Affairs, Congressional Term Limits, 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - Government Affairs, DC Statehood, 1991-1192 (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - Government Affairs, English Language Amendment, 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Government Affairs, Escrow Reform Act of 1991, 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - Government Affairs, House Bank Scandal, 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - Gun Control, General, 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - Gun Control, Against (1 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - Gun Control, Against (2 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Gun Control, Against (3 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Gun Control, Brady Bill (1 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - Gun Control, Brady Bill (2 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Gun Control, Brady Bill (3 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Gun Control, Pro (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Gun Control, Pro (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Gun Control, Student Research, 1992 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Gun Control, Youth Training and Education, 1992 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Health, General (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Health, General (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Health, General (3 of 3), 11991-1992 (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Health, Balanced Budget Act, 1992 (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Health, Family and Medical Leave Act, 1991-1992 (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Health, Girling Health Care, 1991 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Health, Glaucoma, 1992 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Health, Insurance, 1991-1992 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Health, Legislation (1 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Health, Legislation (2 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Health, Legislation (3 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Health, Medical Research, 1992 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Health, Mental Health, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - Health, Nutrition Advertising, 1991-1992 (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Health, Rural Hospitals, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Health, Silicone Response, 1991-1992 (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Housing, 1991-1992 (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Hunger/Poverty, General, 1991-1992 (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - Hunger/Poverty, Childhood Hunger Relief Act, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - Immigration, General, 1991-1992 (Box 265, Folder 8)
    - Insurance, General, 1991-1992 (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - Judicial, General, 1992 (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - Judicial, Clarence Thomas Confirmation, 1991-1992 (Box 265, Folder 11)
    - Judicial, Legal Services, 1991-1992 (Box 265, Folder 12)
    - Labor, General, 1991-1992 (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Labor, Health and Human Services (HHS) Bill, 1991 (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Labor, Occupation Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), 1991DL1992 (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Labor, Strikes (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Labor, Strikes (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Medicare, General, 1991-1992 (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Medicare, Fee Schedule (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Medicare, Fee Schedule (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Medicare, Geographic Data Accuracy Act, 1992 (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Medicare, Health Care Financing Administration, 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Product Liability, 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - Private Property, 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - Religion, General, 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Religion, Religious Freedom Restoration Act, 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Science and Technology, General, 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - Science and Technology, NASA, General, 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - Science and Technology, NASA, Space Station Freedom (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - Science and Technology, NASA, Space Station Freedom (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 267, Folder 11)
    - Seniors, 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Services, Fire Fighters, 1991 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Services, Postal, General, 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Services, Postal, Stamp Tax, 1992 (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Small Business (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Small Business (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Social Security, General, 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - Social Security, Earn Limit, 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Social Security, Government Pension Offset, General, 1991 (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - Social Security, Government Pension Offset, Teacher Retirement, 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 10)
    - Social Security, Notch (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Social Security, Notch (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Social Security, Reform, 1991-1992 (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Social Security, Tax on Benefits, 1992 (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Tax, General (1 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Tax, General (2 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Tax, General (3 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Tax, General (4 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Tax, General (5 of 5), 1991-1992 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Tax, Annuity Tax, 1992 (Box 270, Folder 2)